# Manoj Rahangdale () Featured

Senior Application Engineer seeking roles in Application Development, Application Design, Application Support, Application Engine, Project Management, Product Development, Requirement Analysis, PeopleSoft, PeopleTools, HTML, CSS, SQL



Current Designation: Senior Applications Engineer Total Experience: 9 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Current Company: Oracle India Pvt. Ltd. Notice Period: 15 Days or less

Current Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore Highest Degree: PG Diploma [Advance Computing]

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore,Pune,Mumbai Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: application development, application design, application support, application engine, project management, product

development, requirement analysis, peoplesoft, html, css, sql, peopletools, component

interface, components, fluid, Peoplecode, Process Monitoring, IB

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 22-Jan-21 Last Modified: 22-Jan-21

# Summary

Worked as Senior Application Engineer in Oracle.

Overall, 9.3 years of experience in requirement analysis, design, customization, development, testing, bug fixes and support maintenance activities for Oracle PeopleSoft.

Worked on PeopleTools - Application Designer, Pages, Component, People Code, Fluid pages, Application Engine, Component Interface, SQL, Process Scheduler Manager, Process Monitor, CAPI.

Self-motivated, highly committed to responsibilities.

Have experience in mentoring and managing team members.

# **Work Experience**

Oracle India Pvt. Ltd. as Senior Applications Engineer

Aug 2019 to Till Date

Project 1: PeopleSoft FSCM Product Development (Aug 2019 ? Present)

Company: Oracle Modules: Project Costing

Roles and Responsibilities: Working as a Senior Developer.

? I have worked on Peoplesoft FSCM product development for project costing.

? Worked on new features and bug fixes.

? Involved in Design, Development, Testing, Impact Analysis.

? Migration of the projects to the Master database for targeted PeopleSoft Image.

Major Accomplishments:

? Developed new feature ? ?Update project template status? My Work link under Projects WorkCenter.

? Provided fixes for many bugs.

#### Cognizant Technologies Solutions as Senior Associate

May 2011 to Jul 2019

Project 2: PeopleSoft FSCM - ESA AD (March 2012 - July 2019)

Company: Cognizant

Project Description: We worked on enhancing the functionalities related to Resource Management module in ESA.

Modules: Resource Management and Timesheet.

Role and Responsibilities: Worked as a Senior Developer and Technical Lead.

- \* Involved in Design, Development, Testing, Bug fixes and Enhancement of PeopleSoft Resource Management.
- \* Discussed the requirement with business analyst and prepared Enhancement Bug Fix Report (EBR).
- \* Created and modified the PeopleSoft objects Fields, Records, Pages, Components, Peoplecode, Menu, Permission Lists/Role, Application Engine, CI and File Layout.
- \* Migration of the projects to production instance with the help of CAPI.
- \* Supported system functions that includes Process Monitoring, Application Maintenance and Data Request. Also, involved in monthly maintenance activity on regular basis.
- \* Involvement in requirement discussion calls, provided estimation, task assignment to team members, validation of test cases and its sign off, code review with developer to ensure quality.

Project 3: FOX SOA Support (May 2011 - Feb 2012)

Company: Cognizant

Technologies: Core Java, J2EE, Oracle ADF, Web center, Fusion Middleware, Oracle Access Manager (OAM).

Project Description: The project involves configuration of the OAM with Web center and development of the custom login

Role and Responsibilities:

- \* Involved in requirement analysis.
- \* Analyzed already developed application and given presentation for the same.

#### **Education**

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Electronics/Telecommunication) from Nagpur University in 2010

PG: PG Diploma (Advance Computing) from Sunbeam institute of information and technology in 2011

### IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
PeopleSoft, HTML, CSS, SQL	
Data Mover, SQL Developer, CAPI,	
WinSQL, Fluid Technology,	

## Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak	
English	Proficient				

#### **Affirmative Action**

### **Work Authorization**

Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time